Oh, yes
Then I will come and visit you that day.
I'll ask you again
Yes, thank you, teacher
Yes, please go in.
Who is this morning?
Hospital
It's time to get treatment
Did you sleep well?
Why are you covering up?
too
Is it transparent?
Wow
sleep more
Uh, where are you going?
to feed you
Didn’t you cook rice?
Just wait a moment, I’ll prepare you some food right away.
Should I do it?
I'm really good at mixing water.
Uh, wait
First, dry your hair first.
I have a cold, let's go
While eating?
I can do it
Because I want to do it
Stop being awkward and accept it
yes
Huh?
You have a mole here on the back of your neck...
here, no, no, here
This! It tickles
Did you see the letter?
traitor
I, I told you to watch it by chance, right?
I heard it was prestigious.
The spelling is all right, right?
But
That stationery seemed old.
With the person who wrote the introduction
I heard there’s a different person you’re with right now?
Um...
What are you going to do today?
bouquet practice
Then I
I think we should write a social essay together.
- Fighting!
- Go for it!
Fighting, don't be nervous!
- Carry this.
- Uh
- Carrying
-Thank you
Nuri, let’s fight too
Now
One, two, three!
- Go for it!
thank you
- Hurry up and go in.
- Uh
- thank you
- Yeah, you're good.
- I'll come back.
- Yes
I'm shaking
Would you like to buy some coffee?
The two of you have a private time
I'm going to drink
I have warm coffee
Ah, then I, over there
English breakfast milk tea
without sugar
About 75 degrees so you can drink it right away...
Can I ask you a favor?
Really different...
Huh?
older sister
I just got older
I don't think it's big at all
most days i
I needed comfort
It's true that you are like that.
In the end
I thought I would be next to my sister like this again
When others see
I guess my life is a bit pathetic
But I don't care what others think
Just don't look at me like that, sister.
Did you spray perfume? What do I like?
Yeah
Even if you get tired of me
I think you'll like this smell
I guess you tend to get a little tired of it
lie
Ah, you too.
I am really me too
I feel a little better
This is why at home
You have to have kids, but look
Like this as an excuse
Reconciling haphazardly
If it were like the old days, I wouldn't have been able to do it
child, me
We really are now
I thought they were like a couple
Is that so? A real couple?
uh?
What are you looking for?
Oh, I have to buy English academy textbooks.
Where is the foreign language corner...
Oh my, what is it?
Why is Mr. Joy here?
I stopped by for a moment before going to the academy.
Is there a bookstore near the office?
I love it so much
You must come here often
I didn't get the license to get it.
Ha, this is on the road
keep falling apart
It will be picked soon
The foreign language corner is here.
Mr. Joy, what did you buy?
Ah, that, that, what is it?
Uh, I'm going to buy Taerin's magazine.
Will it take longer to come out?
Still, the attitude of trying to take care of
'Very Delicious'
But what did you buy and hide it?
Ah...
Uh, I actually
Yes, I like doing housework, so I just...
I like you, why do you hide it? Are you embarrassed?
No, I'm confident
Adults, when a man enters the kitchen,
Falling...
There were no such research results?
Was it because my learning experience was short and I couldn’t find it?
I can't even find the textbook right now
Um...
Because it’s this way.
Director, you are wise.
Huh? Was there?
The security guard said
Some guy these days
They say I act strangely every night
When coming and going
Please make sure to report it to me, Mr. Joy.
- Because you never know.
- Yes
Oh, when was the production presentation?
‘Femicide for Love’?
There are still a few weeks left...
No way, drama promotion schedule
Are you preparing already?
Ha, you have to prepare in advance.
It was completely dry when I took the picture.
It can't be blowing
Hey, Nuri!
You worked hard
Kimchi!
Oh, try standing here too.
It's pretty, but the scenery behind it
I'll take a picture for you
Is that so?
- Come to work.
- I charm
- I'll take a picture for you.
- Uh
One, two, three!
Chi, they're playing around, ayu
They say milk tea cannot be made without sugar.
No, you don't have to add sugar.
I'll just have to endure it, well, I'll drink it well.
Oh, it's heavy, right? My brother will listen to you
thank you
I need a bathroom
- I'll come back and drink some coffee.
- Yes
Wow, it's cooled down now.
Did you enjoy the practical skills?
Oh, should I not ask this?
I don't know, actually
The whole time I was filming, I felt a little sad.
It seemed complicated...
Um, I'm thinking of meeting my mom.
Um...
Originally this art
It is born from agony
You decided to meet mom.
yes
The sun has already come
Wow, he was very angry.
Wow, I got caught because of you...
Wow, because of that.
I had a huge fight with my brother.
What are you going to do with this, uncle?
I'm sorry uncle
Oh, you won't be able to hide it till the end
I made a secret for no reason
your mom now
I guess it's become worth living
And then
The longing that I pushed away just comes flooding back
Uncle said that
I am that...
Asking for forgiveness from the sun
Too greedy, right?
Yeah, whatever.
You're going to be hated anyway
What I can do for you
Do everything and get it, okay?
You should do it boldly and courageously
Fight until the end, man.
- Fighting!
- Fighting
Maybe I should have used preserved flowers?
I guess the fresh flowers are from Sydney, so these are
‘Distinguished guests who came today’
No, with lily of the valley.
Should I have done it?
If the diet is simple,
The bouquet is a bit simple...
‘Today’s ceremony is
'It will be held without an officiant'
Oh no
No, ears...
‘Thank you for your precious step’
I don't even care about me
Seong Je-yeon, really.
‘He is today’s protagonist.’
with loud applause
please welcome the bride
Ha...
Now, next
There will be a position for the groom.
groom entrance
no
I am like this
I'm making a bouquet and you're next to me
Because I'm writing something like that
I can't help but think like this.
The groom goes in first.
Because of you, I'm confused about the order.
The bride is the main character.
Even at moments like this
I can concentrate
So, you probably went to Seoul National University.
focus, focus
Ha...
don't do it
Just focus on what you were doing
Stay still
Baby, don't do it.
don't do it
Ah...
Oh, don't do it!
Ah, ah...
There are many things that really interest me.
Isn’t that what you’re asking me to do?
Tell me, I'll do it
- Is it real?
- But
What is this business card?
At that time, ah, when the chair was delivered
Did you receive it?
If you're not going to kiss me, don't worry
I will
Yes
Chi
Kid...
He said he would take a look
I heard you were asking about copyright.
As long as it's okay with you
Rather than selling it to scammers
Director is better
and originally
You were famous for content planning.
When are you going to see me?
I was hoping to see you soon
Because of you, I want to think about it again
Yes
Seong Je-yeon
You're so annoying, you
It's funny because we're in a relationship
What's funny, what?
How funny!
- ah!
- Wait a minute.
- Who is it?
- That's right.
Didn't you say your brother would be late?
With that damn guy
I told you to stay up late and come back
you are here
Uh, what is it? Was there?
Ah, why didn’t you contact me?
Opening the door of someone else's house
Are you just coming in here without permission?
Do you think someone wanted to come?
Mom sent me a package
Eat and leave, this is the refrigerator
Hello...
- Ah!
- Oh, my goodness.
Sorry, I'm so behind...
Brother, I left my luggage here...
Everything?
what?
What is it?
- what?
- Where is this pointing?
Aren't you putting your hand down? Sure
What is it?
The two of us haven't seen each other in a while
How many years have passed...
Wow, what a relationship is...
Easy, easy
What, is it easy?
Hey, we confessed to each other four times in total.
After dumping her three times, we finally got together.
Does this look easy to you?
Oh, it's going to be a struggle?
Hey, Liu Bei also told Zhuge Liang
I only visited three times
Really? Zhuge Liang said that?
People are okay
Ah, ah...
Hey, just hurry and follow me in.
It's good, yes, it's good
sleep, wait a minute
Seokju, would you like some tangerines?
You eat all your share
How has your brother been?
Is the store still busy?
Doesn’t your company have company dinners?
Groups are always welcome
yes
What are you proud of?
Even the numbers you shoveled in
Say goodbye to Kim Seok-ju
What am I worse than Zhuge Liang?
no, i
Because Seok-ju speaks strangely
Did we meet easily?
It's not
Ah!
I can't stay here anymore, I'm embarrassed
Then
How should I go about it in a natural way? huh?
Wait a minute, then
Do you think it was you and me fighting?
Ha, then Mr. Gunno
I think you'll care
Let’s pretend that something urgent happened to me.
Why are you going?
Those people can just leave
You don’t seem to know what you’re hearing?
Wow, crazy about women
Ah... something urgent came up.
I think I should stop and go first.
See you again
Hey, why don’t you practice driving again?
I really have to pick it this time
I got caught by my mom
Ah, this is...
What I didn't win
You talk like you didn’t win because of me.
Pick it yourself
Seong Je-yeon
Can you go alone?
Uh, well, of course.
Yeah
I'll go
See you again
Yeah
Did you hear everything?
It sounded so good
Didn’t I tell you to listen?
I want to be alone
Everyone go out
I’m still going because it’s dirty
brother
Can I take this nutritional supplement?
Oh no, you're overnourished.
Oh, even though I'm like this
It’s an empty gangjeong
Oh no!
What, I guess it’s really good?
eat a lot
Seokju Don’t you know yet?
It's not even a good thing
What are you doing talking about in the neighborhood?
The kid is just surprised
And then you get caught again like I did?
I see you letting go of drugs like that.
I think I'll get caught in the near future.
I was going to take the medicine earlier, but I forgot.
I have to go to the hospital too.
With Seokju at all
Would it be better if we went together?
Ugh
It's been a while!
Long Time No See
- How have you been?
- Uh
Hey, I'm really sorry I'm on vacation.
Part 3 of the movie ‘A World Made of Ashes’
Because of the audition
Oh, you too on the weekend
I went to work, well, it's okay.
Well, they select high school students.
Audition?
Uh, you and Sang-yeop are on your team.
Because there are some young kids
please follow me
This is the audition script...
I understand
Uh, then I'll rent a practice room.
I have to make it properly and send it to you.
Wow, I feel reassured.
How are you?
Is it because you rested or did your face open up?
under! Do you think something is noticeable?
Well, I have some things to unfold.
Hey, hey, come back quickly
Because I'm annoyed, come on
yes
Ah
Have you heard about ‘Kongjwi Patjwi’?
They say there was chaos there.
Patjwi actor
I suddenly quit because I couldn't do it.
Oh my, that's already
Aren't you filming?
They're looking for an actor for the punctured spot.
make an uproar
Ah, our company
There are no suitable actors
That, senior
Give me that script, okay?
The female lead is a third-generation chaebol.
At the beginning of the play, the opponent
Because I fell in love with you so much
You throw everything away
Even if I go back, I will inherit it.
Among the reasons I like it
Some may be chaebols.
Chaebol in Korea
Many settings are also social...
Just criticize society
Can’t I even criticize it?
Hey, let’s order some food.
Taerin’s salad?
Ha, I don't know
chicken feet
Add vermicelli to
Rice balls, no.
Stir-fry it in soup...
Uh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Ah, this
I do this at home
I've been making some
Eh, what is it? Joy, are you good at cooking?
Oh, no, I just, I just like it.
Ah, sister's bet, Taerin's sister's bet
I made it low calorie
Thank you, joy
Look So Delicious
This together
Well!
- Amazing
- Oh, thank goodness.
I wish the books that came in were like this too.
It will come back someday
What stands out
Again?
I'll eat well, Mr. Joy.
It's really delicious
Ugh, it's cold.
Huh?
Ah, we finally met
What is it? Why are you here...
Huh!
What the security guard said
That miscellaneous merchant...
Wow, security guard.
I only gave you three cups of coffee.
You made a miscellaneous merchant.
You came three times?
third time today
On the first day, I came and wandered around.
I got scolded harshly.
I will explain the situation
They gave me some snacks so I ate some.
If that's the case, just come in.
They all know each other anyway.
So it won't work
me
Because it's private life
Please tell me your contact information
I came because I wanted to receive it in person.
So how many days has it been like that?
Wasn’t it cold?
It was cold
When is the time?
I'll check the schedule and let you know.
Would you like a ride?
No, I have overtime.
I have to return to work
I'll go
What is it?
It's cute
Oh yeah, so that
Senior, you know ‘Kim An-min Books’, right?
If you know the representative's contact information...
Bankruptcy?
imprisonment?
Ah, then that company’s publishing rights.
I guess it's all gone?
Work you wish to republish
What exactly is it?
- Ugh
- Let me take a look.
no, that
There is a production company that makes movies.
They probably handled the copyright there.
I'll take care of it, yeah
Ha...
It's being repaired by the HR team.
I know
Still
See you
Written by hand
I wanted to give it to you
Ah, this is from a trip...
Do you want to go on a trip and buy something for me?
Don’t you hate me?
yes
6 years at first job
There was more joy than bad
Including the representative.
I only posted it to the HR team.
I almost felt sad
Until the remaining auditions
I'll finish well
Jeyeonah
I cared about you so much
I know
Don't make yourself lonely
I hope you do
- Are you okay?
- Yes
Oh, then who do you learn from before?
to our team email
I added a supplementary manual.
hello
yes, hello
Oh yeah, here, yeah, there
My sister, please
Please take care of me
-Take some of this...
- Huh? Do you do it, father?
- But who are you?
- Oh, let me say hello...
Ah, yes, I am the representative here...
An people, no
The person who becomes my husband
Oh, yes, please take care of me.
baby, it's okay
There are a lot more in there, right?
hello
- Ah, my friend.
- Yes
It's been a while
Hello
Yes, please have some bread.
Oh, oh, thank you.
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
Who gets permission?
No, I'm your sister's husband.
The secretary sent it to me right away...
Oh, really!
my sister
It looks prettier at work!
Sister!
My sister, you’re so pretty...
Let's go in, let's go in
- Huh?
- Come here!
No, here and now, hello, I...
Yes, fighting today too!
Go for it!
Oh, wait...
I brought this, this
No, you should call this cute.
Should I call you crazy?
They said it would come in the afternoon
Were you the head of the publishing company?
No, you can't come empty handed.
So I did some
Sister, this is delicious, this one...
So why did you come, Mr. President?
Ah, that...
Shall we sit down for a bit?
Well, that...
Produced by my sister's company
I heard the original movie is out of print.
It was published by our publisher
I came here because I wanted to republish it.
Oh, your son's novel
If you republish it when it hits theaters
There's nothing wrong with promoting it together.
But you
Are you interested in republishing it?
First, prepare an alternative
I'm thinking of meeting you
I'm afraid my sister will be uncomfortable
I wanted to get my sister's permission first.
What's there for me to be uncomfortable with?
It's business
I'm the writer
I hope I can convince you well.
The representative
Oh, I also have an alternative to persuade my sister.
I just thought about it and brought it to you
That's why I snack too
I just brought it here like this
It was actually counterproductive.
Let's not do that again
Oh, right, me.
I still handwritten the letter
I couldn't even turn it
I went out for a moment...
Keep this in your heart
don't turn, please
-I wrote this all night...
- Write!
older sister
Oh, sister, what should I do?
Ah, my sister
Hey, why do you want to study?
How did your practical skills go?
Did you see it well?
How do I know?
The judges will know
What are you still looking for?
I found it
to your mother
I want to give you some old photos of you.
You've grown so much
Ha, really
cute
It was really cute this time
don't do it
Do you know where he went?
No, I haven't seen him at all these days.
- Ha, really, where did you go?
- Don't do it.
- Nuri, Nuri.
- Oh, don't do it!
- Oh, why are you like that, really?
- Nuri, where have you gone? It's Nuri
Nuri!
Ah...
What, you didn't push it that hard?
Don't overdo it
What is it?
Where does it really hurt? uh?
brother
What's wrong?
uh?
who?
I, by any chance
Have you ever seen our network?
It looks like this
Oh, really!
Don't talk to me for a week
Why are you like that, really?
Hey, over there
Hey, have you ever seen this guy?
Nuri, you have to come home!
Call me when you're done
My brother will come pick you up.
- Uh, Nuri.
- uh?
This
- Hello
- Hello.
Oh, are you here?
- What about Sang-yeop?
- They say they're a little late because there's traffic.
Uh, then
As announced in the group chat room,
Let’s all be partners today
And personal practice time
one hour at a time
Question?
Team leader, are you quitting the company?
Yeah
this is my last job
Audition schedule is all mine
I'll back it up for you, so don't worry.
Now, let’s start with practice
Oh, it's me
What are you doing the day after tomorrow?
Oh, why?
Ah...
I'm not feeling well
I'm going to the hospital
Please come with me
Age when a guardian is needed
Isn't it?
Are you under anesthesia for sleep?
I can't drive anyway, you know
Needed to drive
I probably didn't call you
Just do it
Oh, I have an appointment that day.
What time is the treatment?
I'll match my brother.
I'll text you, thank you
Yeah
Oh my, really...
Would you like to put it in a vase instead of roses?
Red-faced?
Director, when are you free?
There's something I'd like to discuss.
uh
me today
Can't I sleep with my mom?
I just wanted to talk more.
Uh, yeah
How should I give you a ride?
He said he brought a car.
yes
Eat delicious food with your mother
I will take good care of you too.
What are you doing? Go quickly, I'll be waiting for you.
- Yes
- Eat something delicious.
‘I made a fuss and sold it.
At best, they even gave me a refund.'
‘Ah, just looking at the rolling dust
'I'm the one who's going to be angry'
Is it going to be him?
who are you?
It's delivery. You ordered chicken feet, right?
yes? I don't do anything...
Are you Seonwoo?
uh?
It's delivery
Ah, no...
Why suddenly...
Uh, how did you get here, huh?
No, that...
Wow
It looks like this
No...
No, without saying a word
Why did you come so suddenly, huh?
What if it comes like this?
Oh, you ordered chicken feet, right?
Because this is my first time coming to your house
I was thinking about buying something
Ah...
I always need toilet paper, thank you
Oh, really
But why all of a sudden, what happened?
Because I miss you
What is it? Excitedly
But I was monitoring this
I have to finish it
It won't take much time, just
I want to go in and see your face
- Good.
- Huh?
This was delivered today
The last time I went to your house, it wasn't there.
It is a necessity for modern people.
Take it with you when you come
What is this?
- Robot vacuum cleaner?
- Yes
Hey, this expensive thing...
No, this is still
I bought it cheaply on a deal.
Oh, people can do the cleaning.
Oh, return this quickly, you.
Really?
- I told you to do it.
- No, this.
They say it’s really easy to use
Ha, really, Seong Je-yeon
Ah
I bought this to give to you
What is it?
what's this?
Oh my, what is this?
pretty
ladle saucer
I bought it really cheap, 50,000 won
Eh? Is this 50,000 won?
Hey, this
You should refund this, right?
What kind of ladle-like sound...
Wait a minute, I'm just on the phone
Uh, hello?
Uh, uh, I was just watching
I monitor all of this.
Let's have a video meeting, uh
Anyway, it's shabby here, but please sit down.
Well, would you like some coffee?
no
Look at my work, I'll go, okay
Ah...
Huh?
That...
When are you going to see the doctor?
Shall I go with you?
I have a lot of time
Um...
It doesn't seem to be there
Ha...
Don't worry
Seokju decided to go together.
Then...
Shall we see you after the treatment?
I'll buy you something delicious
Uh, this is the money I refunded.
Then
I ate it deliciously
Do you remember what we did?
When I load and unload a delivery
ok
I'm really going
goodbye
- Huh?
- Don't go.
hello
- Hello
-What is it?
Is there nothing but joy?
It's smoking time for you two now.
- Please sit down.
- Yes
Are you here?
your face has improved
Really?
I guess I'm a little happy these days
Why am I happy, why do I know?
It's me
Oh wait, I got a text message.
I practiced driving
They said they would give it to you
I'll give you stock information and get rid of it.
I'll see you after work.
call
What is it, Kim Seok-ju?
Yes, I have to get the money taken.
You pay no attention to him
How can I turn off your interest when you say you're my fan?
- He's your fan?
- huh!
Even taking one picture
He was very embarrassed.
No, no, I
That's enough about Kim Seok-ju.
That, patjwi actor
Did you hear about my departure?
That
Can’t Taerin do it?
Director, what do you think?
Still, there yesterday
I got a call asking about Motaerin's schedule.
Well, if it’s Kwon Do-eun and director Han Seung-yoon,
It's a work you don't want to miss.
Because the work is good, I
This is what Taerin wanted to do.
Ah...
For the first time in a while, we agree?
But at the work site
Intermediate input at this point
It's a burden for my actor.
Nevertheless, I
What if I say that?
Ah...
Let's Go
Are you really okay?
I kept thinking about it too
I met him and he said, “I’m not that good.”
If you don't
I can't help it anymore
Let's go
- Let's Go
Let's Go
No, information that can be given by text message
Why bother meeting?
I guess I asked to meet him because I deserved to meet him.
Hmm, is it delicious?
Even if you eat it just once, you get a full meal...
Hey, watch and learn.
You posted it, right? uh?
This
Take a picture and take it
Take soybean powder
Well!
If you know how to do something
He ate it while showing off his pride.
Same with driving
Mmm, so delicious
Wow
If I work in entertainment
Do you think you'll do well?
you?
Arthur, Arthur
What is it? Are you serious?
If you're asking seriously, well
Oh my gosh
They say nothing in this world is easy
You have a weak stomach, you only study
Hey, just live by the numbers
Will my mom leave me alone?
Oh, I shouldn't have stood out that day.
Ah...
Please take a step back
I don't think we can do it all together
Exactly how many?
Brother, I'm here!
Uh, teacher
Teacher, what are you doing here? uh?
I want to eat Mr. Geonno’s meal.
Ah...
Because I don't know when I'll eat again
I'm going to Australia
Australia?
- yes?
- Oh, I don't know.
I canceled my flight, so don’t stop me.
Goodbye, Joseon!
No, no
Jin, did you really mean to leave?
- uh?
- Oh, don't go, sir!
don't go
Oops
Did you spill everything?
Ah, Gunno, why are you like this? It's the main policy
Ah, why did we see each other so often?
No, to open makgeolli
How many times have you been here?
I felt proud and happy inside.
Yes, have some makgeolli.
Where are you going?
You don’t even speak English.
Ah, hey!
Would you like to give it to the bookstore?
Sometimes I go and do some cleaning.
I'm not going to dispose of it and leave it alone.
Because it’s my grandmother’s will
I don't like it
Wow, I...
I'm upset, again, that, hey!
Come visit Australia, my brother and I
I will become a surfing master
- Mr. Gunno
- Yes
I flipped it over on purpose, right?
Let's do it again
- Teacher, teacher
- Huh?
Oh, can you go alone? uh?
I heard you were drinking too much makgeolli earlier.
Wow, the smell, really
Oh, come on, I'll take you there.
Hey, hey, hey!
It's in front of me, well
Hey
Even if you do, please clean up the bookstore.
So, while cleaning
It's your writing, this
What if I miss you?
Boy, it's so far away, really
Just make a video call
Hey, hey, why does it tickle, why are you like this?
Going
Ah...
I'll take you there
Ah, teacher!
How are you feeling these days?
Paresthesia or dizziness
It seems to be happening quite often these days.
- Are you taking your medicine well?
- Yes
Have you ever vomited after taking it?
Not there yet?
yes
This time, a clinical trial
It's progressing.
Not domestically
The patient's case is very rare.
Even if complete cure is difficult
The severity of symptoms may be alleviated
Hey
Hey, Seokju.
No, I know better than I explain.
To the doctor
I thought it would be better to listen right away
Are you very surprised?
I'm surprised
Does Nuri know? Brother, you're sick
There is a college entrance exam to enjoy, right?
It doesn't interfere with studying
It wasn't long before the disease progressed.
From long ago
I think I thought a day like this would come
Oh, just
Don't be too surprised
No matter what happens
Are you not surprised if you know?
Just be surprised in advance
No, my brother...
Do you know why I liked you?
I
My brother changed my life
For making it a little complicated
My brother accepts me well
But
My life is getting complicated...
There were many simple times
yes thanks
Go bro
I think I'll look ugly
Are you really going?
Oh, go
Now the customer
Can't answer the phone...
Are you sure you gave me the correct address?
It looks like a hospital here
Are you crying?
What can I do for you?
I know because I’ve wet it a lot.
Just go and ask why you're crying
Rather than comforting
If only I had left it alone
There are times when I want to
I'll just have to do what I want.
Um...
Because I'm cold
Could it be an icicle?
Ugh, it's cold
alcohol
Do you know how to drink?
Do you know how to eat chicken feet?
yes, what
Are these really chicken feet?
Arrived at destination
End route guidance
- Is this right here?
- Uh
They say the navigation is correct.
It doesn't seem like an extension, does it?
Is it gone?
Ha, it didn't taste good
- You said it was delicious?
- I'm going to pretend it never happened.
- What did you say it was a store?
- Baekban House
Wow, it sounds so delicious!
No, how many side dishes were there?
What is the main one?
Calm down and let's go in first.
You're hungry, huh?
thank you
I also ordered ice cream.
Well done as expected
Ah, but today
The time has come, it's a weekday?
Yeah, one audition.
I'm free except for getting ready.
uh
Why do I have so much time?
Aren’t you curious?
I'm curious
Yes, that's right
I'm the most curious person in the world
me
I quit the company
Huh?
Well, because I achieved the final result.
Don't worry
I'm worried
How do we feed them?
I heard you eat a lot.
Don't starve, I like rice
Ha...
Why did that white house disappear?
They give me rice there.
If you quit
Something just happened
I felt like I was wandering like the old days
But something
Ah, something about that feeling...
Somehow
Um...
You look relieved
Yeah
- I think so.
- Yes
Of course
At the end of this unemployed person's road
I'm not sure what there is
But
Because you are there
Just, whatever.
If there is one landmark
Could this be a pretty good milestone?
Am I a landmark?
No, Bulguksa Temple
How does that become your milestone?
I should be good enough
Huh? Wait a minute
Huh? Who is it?
Sangyeopi
It's okay, baby
Thank you
Ha...
It's no big deal, kid...
‘Sister, you’ve worked hard all this time.
'I will definitely pass this audition'
‘See you that day, good luck to you too, sister’
No, to ‘Goodbye’
Do you really need hearts?
Oh, and haven't you gone to the military yet?
Ah, I have to do one more project.
That's 'a world made of ashes'
Part 3 would be perfect
The original author was involved in the casting.
Can you get involved?
- No
- Oh, I should have put it in the contract.
Well, don't reply
If you reply, when he goes to the army and marches
Just think about yourself, don't
Well, is that okay?
I can't, never
- Oh my, my, my, my.
- No.
Huh? It's business, business
Okay, then I'll do it while you watch.
Now, ‘Sang-yeop, you worked hard’
Okay, don't watch it.
Why did I order it like this?
It's not coming out?
I'll come check it out
Finish it quickly until then
Yep
Oh, and
no long sentences
In short answer form
Oh my, that damn march
uh, thank you
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you
Wow
What's wrong? Are you dizzy?
uh
I guess I failed
Do you want to eat this first?
I'll go and wash my face.
Is this a loss of sugar?
I don't know if I'm sleepy
It gets better if you wash your face
Is it okay if I don’t go with you?
Where? In the men's bathroom?
uh
I've wanted to go since I was young
Chi
please stay here
Don't wait in front
I'll be back soon
The bathroom is being repaired.
I think I need to go back a little further.
Isn't it here?
Hello, me
How many bathrooms are there by any chance here?
There are each floor
There is no password
So, are there any places that are being repaired?
No, everything is fine
It's available
thank you
yes, thank you
Are you here?
I...
Don't be angry
calm down and listen
Ah...
There was a real situation
Yeah
This place is too wide
It's my first time here
I wandered for a while
So I'll go with you
Are you directionless?
Uh, right
Ha...
From next time you
I have to do as I'm told.
Oh, but not in the men's restroom.
I'm not going
I'm not curious, there it is now
It's snowing
It's true
That's right
I guess it’s the first snow
I guess so
Sister, it's snowing
No more documents now
I recommend looking out the window
It's snow
Will it pile up?
Let's build a snowman together
Either that
Ha...
The whole world will turn white
- Thank you, yes.
- Yes, enjoy, thank you.
- Sell a lot
- Yes, thank you.
Oh!
Baby, let’s eat
Mr. Joy
Aren’t you hungry?
I heard you will see it all today.
After eating
Oh, I'll finish watching after eating.
Huh? Uh...
Eat while reading, I
Bring all the coal jars together
I brought a packed lunch.
Taerin, finally
Because I think I can enter the work.
I'm so excited
out of pure kindness
You think I can’t even get angry, do you?
I'm not that kind of person
Uh, it's snowing.
Look at the snow and feel better
Just 10 minutes
I am unaffiliated
Who gives the snow?
I want to thank him
- Oh!
- oh!
wow!
What, you did great.
One, two, three!
How do you eat an entire plate?
This is for 1 person.
I tried a few chopsticks and there were none.
Do you want to eat something?
I hope you read it if you have it
Odeng soup
The end?
I wish I could eat more
Ha...
'Assorted skewers 12,000 won
Egg roll 8,000 won'
‘Separate cost for additional cheese’
‘Pyeonmeat, chicken feet’
You just ate the chicken feet
Ha, that's really funny
Why order it, why read it?
You're laughing
I guess you're feeling better
With that feeling, you have to choose a snack now.
This is separate from feeling better
no matter what happens
I wanted to hold hands today
Are we ready?
- Of course not.
- Then what is this?
braided!
Snow will pile up today
What if the road freezes?
That's right
Ho! like! like!
I remember
Even in the past
I blew it so hard
Get well soon
You should blow like this
Not with vocalization, but with breathing.
we feel stupid
What?
I'm not stupid
Usually idiots
That's what he said the most
Chi
I think I understand now
Huh?
If you're too happy
There are times when it's scary
when and where
No matter how we met
I wouldn't have turned around
It would have been irreversible
This heart
What should we do?
It is definitely recommended to go.
You have to go far to get well
Oh, what should I do...
What should I do, brother?
Even if I die, I want to be here
With my people
I don't want to break up with Hae.
What if something goes wrong there?
Some times are still
Maybe forever
Maybe this moment